Hi!
Something that you're going to want to remember is that it takes very, very little water for a child to drown.
A couple of inches is all that they need.
A crawler can very easily crawl into the kitchen.
Remember, babies are kind of top heavy.
A crawler can actually tip over into a bucket and drown with just a couple of inches of water.
If you're cleaning your kitchen and mopping the floor, you want to be really careful that you have kept your child out of the area.
Whether it's putting him in his crib or playpen, or gating it off with the baby gates that we have discussed.
It just takes one second, one phone call, for you to run off, grab the phone quick, and a child can come in and find his way to the bucket, and it could end tragically.
Remember that you always want to be very careful of whatever bodies of water.
It doesn't take much for a child to drown.
Be sure that all of the buckets are either up out of baby's reach or that your child is secured out away from the kitchen if you're cleaning.